hi welcome
welcome to Dandan nice to be here
thank you Michelle
yeah and Valentina here
welcome to Dandan hello
how's it going hi
nice to meet you good to see you
oh you're so pretty
oh thank you
yeah she is okay
this place is crazy like it isn't it cool
thank you
you wanna try a banana latte
banana I think this is the banana one
that's really good
it's like not too banana E
I wish it was more banana E
can I have more of your latte
yeah
I can't reach it
are you buttoning it all I don't know
I think it's fun
hello
nice to see you
we are going to go to the consultation room for
so how are you doing we're doing great
it's really nice today so how do you feel about makeover
I'm excited I'm really excited too
really I've never had any makeup on
and so I'm very interested to see what this is
your first time doing makeup
first time ever doing makeup
OK yeah great
so
oh it's your taekwondo
yeah I'm a taekwondo athlete
I've been I've been doing taekwondo uh
since I was like 4 4
4 years old yeah
my name is I'm Mitchell Toomey
I'm a student at New York University currently studying psychology
I'm a taekwondo competitor
I've been doing that since I was 4 years old
we like to party we like to party and we like to get down
you can jump
we're perfect yeah
we busted when we
I was really energetic as a kid
and so my mom asked me to be put into taekwondo
because she heard that it helps kids to develop with discipline and
like concentration
so past I have been ranked um No. 1 in the country
so this year I won the college national championship
I won first place so um
first person thank you
yeah thank you OK
so it's your birthday today is my birthday today yeah congratulations
yeah thank you very much
I appreciate it OK
so you're you're going to party
yeah with your friends
so we have a a party plan for tonight uh
it's gonna be my birthday party
all my friends are gonna be there and everything
and so I just kind of wanted to
to see how that would make my friends react and everything OK
so we'll see you know OK
I see yeah
so Valentina hahaha
you're already beautiful the way you are
oh my gosh your skin is great and looks like also from my mom probably
yeah you guys are blessed
you got blessed for sure yeah for sure
my name is Mitchell to me
and I'm here with my girlfriend Valentina right now
um and I have my birthday party tonight
be fun for like both of us get like our hair and makeup done
I wanted to have some a new look
so have a seat
sure too
you're gonna make up first alright
OK
I don't I like the way that my hair is shaped yeah
but it needs to be trimmed a little bit OK
so your spec line is more than happy
so I trim the clean up the this here okay
and then next styling perfect okay
there you go thank you thank you
I using the this technique
same is a point to cut this line is in smooth change the smooth
it's not blunt to your shape
you keep running circle do you live around here
I live in New Jersey hmm
I heard this New Jersey many live in Korea
it's right yes yeah
there's a lot of people from New Jersey that are uh
Korean um
that's why I think Tae taekwondo is really popular in New Jersey ah
I was wondering why is taekwondo
yeah uh
is popular in USA it's a sport that creates a sense of respect yes
that a lot of a lot of other American sports don't have so interesting
yeah in korea 90
80% is Chinese long taekwondo really
yeah that's so cool because I
I wish that everyone can do taekwondo here
I think that it would be a much better country
if everyone could do taekwondo
Because just the way that it creates you as a person
I think it's a
it would be a very valuable experience for everyone to have
but so amazing it's very popular is to take on the wow
Okay, it's over. Yes, just wait a minute.
Let's Lu Red Bean Lens Your Okay Okay
I'm just happy, just once
Wow softly
Just happiness
You can do it. Wait a minute. Oh, you have to wait a while. What is it? Missionary, you have to wait a while.
I have to do it after my soul calls. Yes, that's right. It's too late by thirty minutes.
a little bit different OK
style do whatever do you like yes and I want to
hey I'm so sorry for the delay no
But
But you don't have to shampoo this.
I have to use this person. No, this is the cloud.
Please give me that wig, I will do it. Ah, okay, just ask for the conditioner. Just the conditioner.
so here please make sure thank you
can you wait for a bit please OK sorry about that that's OK
Then
I don't even have my head here
Let it dry and just let it go naturally, but for now,
I don't know, the teacher. It took a little bit. Should I ask?
Should I stop him and make him wait or
I'm just going to dry it. Oh really.
Damn, I really sing them in order.
It's right to leave first. In front of me, yes, that person is very strict. I think it will take two hours.
I think it will take now
Go in, yes, no, this person can just do his hair and wait. He has to wait.
yes i understand
Thank you. Now, let’s stop this.
Let's stop it together
If I did this wrong, I wouldn't
It's okay. The schedule shouldn't have been like this. It was originally big.
'Cause it seems like it's taking too long, it doesn't make sense now
But fortunately, my girlfriend has good skin, so I think it will heal quickly.
A call to know what it is ah then it will be ok uh man ah girlfriend
I'm wearing makeup right now so hurry up
I think it will end and I'm glad this boyfriend has good skin too.
If I have good skin, it will end quickly. My boyfriend sends me out. My boyfriend
It's a phone. My boyfriend is a phone.
The more my hands go, the more I sing now.
It will take too long. Then, if Leo J does two people,
That's fine, Leo J can take charge of the couple. Oh, that's fine.
I think so. Now, I have to ask a question and then go. Uh, then I'll finish.
I think I can finish it
So it won't take long for this person to
I don't think it will take a long time, then.
Sister, I asked you a favor and said, why don't you get rid of that couple's legos?
So, I think it would be perfect for my sister to be the last customer.
Is it possible to do that?
Well, because I like waiting for that person, I'll eat it.
No, it feels good, so it ends quickly, so...
I think I can do it. Yeah, yeah.
You have nipples. Now, can you be my boyfriend? Can you be my boyfriend?
Aladdin Korea
Yes, that couple is a couple
Yes, it ended quickly and I came back. I see, that’s why.
So Leo J said yes, they were all couples, originally they were one by one, and
I think Pony will be the last guest.
Oh, let's change this. Your couple is just good at Ready.
Ah, it's almost Valentine's Day
It's over. Yes, then it's okay for the pony. Yes, mmmmmm.
Hyewon can do it with my help.
Okay hehe wheat
But should I go get my hair done now?
I'm not leaving now. I have to hide my boyfriend. Oh, that's right.
Yeah, so right now, we're together
I can't see it
I have to do that, but I have to make sure these two can't see each other.
He said I shouldn't be able to see him with my boyfriend. Wait a minute, professor. Please close the door.
Guido can you come over here please yeah yeah cause you got a high
yeah you gotta stay here yeah yeah alright alright
just let me know when I come out alright
alright excuse me
now
alright let's go
let's go let's go
thank you so fast okay
alright
아 아 저기요 오케이 남자친구 어디 계세요 화장실 아 아하하 여기서
기다려서
Mitch are you done yeah yeah
don't look look right don't look right just just do it just do it
yeah yeah
here here here yeah welcome to my room hi
thank you
just meaning wait
hello
oh you're pretty
hey nice to meet you nice to meet you too yeah
happy birthday thank you very much I appreciate it
I'm really excited to be here I've never had any makeup
so this looks really interesting to me is this first time
you make up yeah I've never had makeup done in general wow
this will be the first time for anything how would it be possible
yeah I mean I think I trust you more than anybody
so let's see how it goes
oh my bitch is too much I see it too yeah
also
I'm a rich man I don't care myself
I'm a rich man I'm my own biggest fan I'm a high end demand
I'm a rich man also I'm a rich man I don't care about what they say
9 million look more than a good day make us a
and see my name is where my name is I am a rich man
that's me not a reckless yeah
couldn't mental could got them on me
I got money good I got for your down sign pure gone
your exit is my next stop dancing on my
oh yeah the colors go well
do you know the K pop stars
I don't know many I honestly not really
but like I know more so about like uh
Korean taekwondo stars like yeah
uh Lee Dae hoon
Lee Dae hoon yeah
he's an incredible fighter
and Park Tae Jun he's young
but he's very good what is Park Tae Jun
Park Tae Jun he's a type 1 dough fighter oh um
but he's he's been winning a lot of recent competitions wow
he's very very good yeah
I think I I should try to learn some Korean at least a little bit
you know I can count to 10 10 yeah
say it 1 2
3 4 5 6
7 8
9 10
11 12 wow
perfect yeah perfect
it's OK but I need a you know
I can I can barely say anything else OK
so aniyo aniyo wow
oh yeah that looks so nice yeah
my goodness people really like it
I think it looks really good
actually I don't want to put a lot of things on your face okay
yeah but because hair done maybe complete your look not makeup
I do like I just wanna see what it would look like with more makeup
you know what I mean I like the way this looks
but just to add like something that would like make it very noticeable
uh huh so blush
what do you think yeah
uh okay
do you think so I think when I
when I see you I notice you wear a eye makeup right now because ready
red red colors on your underneath
but us but yeah
that's me I
I because of me
yeah yeah
that's why I I know that
you made it already hahaha you made it
your eyebrow color change
sure that's it cool
it turns out red lip color
I do like I just wanna see what it would look like with more makeup
you know what I mean uh huh
I like the way this looks
I think this is more makeup than I've ever had on
I tried to keep it very neat. It was just a date and a little bit.
But now it was my birthday, yeah
Ah, but why are you doing this? I don’t know what I’ve been doing. Ah, what are you doing?
I'm asking for it, I like the way that this looks for sure
okay give me a second okay sure
It's all over, but I want to put on a little more makeup because I can't do it.
You're good, yes.
But I'm not sure where I should do more right now, so I'm going to ask a question.
now it's so sexy it looks good right
Uh what do you want to more
I don’t know Hahaha
Sister, I need help. Uh yes, sister, hello.
Yes, she has all her makeup done, but yes.
He said he wants to wear more makeup so that other people can recognize him.
Yes, so I would like you to give me some more information on what I can do.
Because if you look at the eye makeup now, Close Eyes Please
Okay, I just added some color like this. Close Open Eyes Please
If you look a little bit now
You did something like this that made you feel like an idol, yes, but something was just right at a glance.
I want you to wear makeup so I can recognize you.
Do you like it? Give me your opinion
what do you think maybe I think you look great yeah but
a little bit of eyebrows a little bit too thick
I like the way that the eyebrows look oh OK but I mean you know
so what which point you know no I
everything that is right now looks
looks great looks great but you need a
little kick for it yeah little kick I think so yeah little kick
what about like the
like mascara mascara huh
is it okay to put a little blinks here you know sure like a
why not oh sure or you I I think you want a deep deep eye right
I think so darker yeah yes darker yeah and a little K paper wire wire
by yeah yes that's so cool right yeah that's so cool
right right I guess I'm just smoking a little
bit
more
a little bit more and then I'm just going to put
Is this something like a Halloween party?
What was it like? Ah, but
Now I know what you want. Do you want your eyes to be a little bit more deteriorated or something?
I said so
And at a glance, I saw that she had put on makeup.
I hope you find out because oh, I've been waiting for such a long time
Make-up at best
I received it, but it can't be revealed. So, what should I do?
I was thinking about doing it, but now it's a little more shadow
Let's put it in and make it a little deeper.
what is thing
looks more I like it more dip yeah yeah that's the
it was cool to watch like the progression of like
at first it didn't even look like he was doing anything
um but then like it started to appear slowly
and like every time he added
another layer I could start to see it come out
I think we're done nice uh huh
um and then eventually like
I just felt like I was a different person all of a sudden
let's go to hair done and I will fix your makeup later okay okay sure
let's go let's do it
Michelle Whoo hey
happy birthday to you happy birthday to you
happy birthday to you happy birthday
to
you which I grab a sit sure yeah yeah
you know what you should close your eyes I should yeah OK
yeah hey hey hey
your escape boyfriend is very different to personalities yes wow yeah
that's why we like each other so much wow so much
I love being around her
she's the best like I can you know just I never never get
tired of being around her it's always so easy
she's a
she she never has like an extreme reaction to anything
she's so chill anytime she reacts to something it's always very calm
is is
is Valentina gonna come out
yes OK
should I look at her as she comes out or wait
uh you have to cover your eyes OK
가 옴니까 두구 두구 두구 두구 두구 두구 두구 제발 이거 오우 노 노 노
um and I have my birthday party tonight
I wanted to have some type of new look that I've never had
when I close
those days will come yet
you're still an open part of me
it's the way
wow
so beautiful yeah damn
oh yeah
I don't have more time
Well, I wanted to give that kind of feeling to the couple. The heart went just right, but now it's time to put on makeup.
If this is a couple,
You guys are Twin, you're so cute when you do things like this
oh my god what do you think
did you choose that oh my god copper pots
oh my God I've never seen you with this much makeup on that's for sure
I like the sparkles
I like your hair yeah it looks different
it's beautiful
I think that we're gonna get some amazing reactions at my party
tonight yeah
Everybody's I can't wait to see what Jack and Steven say like
they're gonna be they're gonna go crazy I think they're gonna yeah
all we need is here among
us hanging out with my best friends
living it up in the endless summer every day is the weekend
Kano Department Kay
What's the makeup? Haha, it's beautiful baby
Okay
Okay, look at your face. It's really, really cute.
It looks like a baby. Go and have a look.
hi hi thank you
have a seat here
hi hi oh my God I love your freckles oh thank you so much
oh my god you're so cute thank you
um so I'm Brianna Grace 17 years old and I'm a student
I'm going into college this is gonna be my first year
I'm planning to be a nursing major
I love helping people so that's what really got me into it
I was looking for a lot more beauty tips
I was looking for also a change in my appearance
I never do stuff like this usually I'm more natural
I've always had the exact
same look for so many years and I wanted something different
it's my it's my time
all night and all night hey OK let's do this
okay first we have to remove the baby hair on your eyebrow okay
haha
or some drink drink one oh not right now no thank you haha
oh
yesterday is I look out your hair like Francis I show you this in here
yeah that's how my hair looks yes
hmm and another style I recommend
I could straighten it
ah do you want to straighten hair ah
OK cause I usually don't straighten my hair
I usually keep it curly many many
yeah OK I can do it OK yes thank you yes just to and
Oh wait a minute
This
I need to straighten it out. I need to change my bangs to a bigger one. Can you just get me a hair dryer?
Yes there is
The thing I was most worried about when I came here was my flowing hair.
Black people have their own hair salon.
It's a special salon, so only black people
There is a separate hair salon here that I go to, so actually.
Korean hair doesn't have noodles like that. It's all there from the roots like this.
Hair changes depending on race
There are widths ranging from one to three. In the case of One A, the safe straight hair starts from three.
The curls are starting to start in earnest. This guy is wearing three coats. The curls are starting to start in earnest.
Actually, this is black hair curly
us
It's not like you're blooming straight, so Jay's ultimate posey again
I've been practicing
But it's difficult
this is a coconut oil OK yes
hmm I love the smell oh no oh my God the smell is so
People with strong curly hair like this shouldn't just run at once.
There's coconut oil and olive oil.
If it's really edible, you have to apply it to your scalp and hair and touch it with ice.
it's too special today mm hmm
I'm so puppy yeah I'm so puppy yeah
We have to take a good look now. We are here.
People passing by: Teacher Cha Hong's great challenge has begun, so this is it now
It's Chahong Thyme. Normally, when it blooms, it doesn't straighten the hair.
You can't open it all at once, you have to fold it in two.
Your dryer is a dryer. Your dryer is a dryer.
Um, wait a minute.
Wow, it takes a lot of strength.
This works. It works. I really like this.
What are you really hahaha
Food um haha wow you are always like this haha you are amazing as expected
Try this out, but for now, just
I gained almost 80 kilos. You don't have to do that. You don't have to do that. Try this one. But
First of all, I just weighed about 80 kilos.
Even if you don't do that
It's okay
My wrist is okay, teacher. It’s okay.
Um, I'm really sleepy
you must be tired no I just like closing my eyes
Oh, I'm really good. Oh, I'm really good. No, I really can't.
OK okay
Brianna don’t know
this yes this smoke is bad smoke
No, the moisture in the coconut oil evaporates.
Hey
It's pretty, okay. When customers see it, they think it's a head tent, so they'll misunderstand it.
You can do this, but feel the texture of your hair now.
We have changed so brilliantly, um au
It's moist. I really like using coconut oil. Real coconut oil.
There are edible ones, yes, edible ones.
oh wow it's very pretty hmm it's good it's good it's too good
oh wow you're a lady have haha
it's so cute
hmm it's too thin I need it
hmm do you want some the vibe like a hot girl or just a natural look
yeah I'm a hot girl really really yeah hahaha
Should I eat this? Look at it. It’s pretty. It’s crazy. The design is really pretty. Oh my god.
let's go It's completely self-made
oh looks nice
Woo
Why are you like this? I just went boldly and dressed up in this color.
Oh, it's a mess, it's a mess, oh my oh my
God hey who are you
Haha, it's so pretty. Why, if you do it well, it's so pretty, so pretty, so pretty.
Brianna is coming
close your eyes already is she coming now Mama she's coming soon Mama
she's coming soon yeah yeah
ah ah
is she coming right now
she's coming
yes she's coming
우우 엄마 와우 와
and I wanted something different
I had curly hair forever obviously
and I just never really knew how to take care of it
I feel like I look at the same thing every single day
as long as it's not the same thing I'm fine with it
so I heard about this I was like I have to go to it
oh my God
yes
yes girl
oh my God
thank you
it's chain No. 6 ready
camera
everybody on the blue action
let's get famous
you hear that everybody yelling action
screaming like a thriller
keep the money nice
oh my God
so I feel like it makes it look like more out there
and I think that's why I like the look so much
so it feels kind of like edgy to it too
and I'm very very happy
she found her new character
yes
yes girl
oh my god
yes yes
girl oh my god
looks so good sister says she's pretty
it's like Ana's room got so much better
let me see
hahaha
wow we love it wow
is it good yes
it looks pretty flawless thank you
oh my god
it's different
good job
thank you so much for coming today
thank you so much thank you
have a good dinner thank you
OK thank you guys
bye bye
have a good evening thank you
have a good evening bye bye
thank you
Oh my, it’s over. It was good. It was good. Yes, it was really good. Salty salty salty flower
I'm salty
Now, just take care of yourselves.
I came in when the sun was shining. Wow, I really can't believe it. It's my order day.
Oh, you worked hard. Let’s toast. Let’s toast. Thank you for your hard work.
You're having a hard time now.
Almost halfway, I came, I dug, I dug, because our hands match.
It ends early. Please send the actual pledge quickly. It looks amazing. Ah, eat it.
Hey sister, let me see. I also saw the pledge.
Um, delicious, delicious, um
There is nothing. Yes, there is nothing. If it’s mine, if it’s mine, it’s delicious. Yes, it’s delicious.
It's delicious, yeah
I like this the most, this is the most delicious
I have a taste for Korea. Korean taste is so good. Buldak tastes like Thai drink.
I really like it
Since we are going to meet together, I have a lot of sense and
Will you grow well and who will you marry?
The woman's eyes were blown away. Um, that's right. The woman's eyes were blown. Wow.
Um um no I actually I actually
When we first had that meeting, when we had our first meeting, now
This is the first time in a long time that I have seen a male actor this close.
But oh, it makes sense haha.
That little bit
That place is so embarrassing. It's my first time seeing it, so the only thing I can concentrate on is eating.
That was all I had, so I kept eating it.
That's right, it's history. No no, what should I do? I'm so happy to see you no no no
yes
weight
I didn't like it when I saw it. It's really good this time.
You just patted your stomach and said haha. So, you really know sugar.
How good is this time?
I'm talking now
So I'm talking about my first impression when I first saw it.
Talk about your first impression. Oh, it's fun. It's fun. I want to hear my first impression too, but I'm
When I just felt it, it was just a quiet, alone world like this.
I had this feeling, but my sister
Even on YouTube, I don't really do vlogs anymore.
Lee Mi-ja on YouTube is so chic. Oh, really.
This is a makeup recommendation. Hello, this is my phone. I do this type of thing a lot.
That's it
Why hello, hello, this is my phone haha. I don’t remember when we first met.
It's me, my sister prepared a lot and that too
I was really surprised. I thought it was awesome because you were prepared.
Everything
You are so active, you really look like a racehorse.
W You’re looking right here, so here
I can't see any difference. They say that's how it is. They all say it's Gyeongju, so people around me
You need to have friends who can do this with you.
So that good friend
When we meet, we get along really well. That's right. Ah, but Jeongyoung is so great.
You helped me a lot, Minyoung here helped me, the CEO helped me, and the two of you also helped me.
I'm just shaking my head and putting on all my makeup
But actually, the one who looks the most different here is Leo.
Leo is also very pure.
I think I'll have a lot of fun when I win
He has a lot of talent, but he's a lot more pure in camera than I thought. Oh, and
I think my personality and personality are really flexible.
Me, uh, thank you haha, good job man haha, that's really funny.
Let’s go. Let’s go. The weather is nice.
Oh, but what the heck, the run is that short, no, we ah
Is it twenty-five kilograms? Is it twenty kilograms? Is it twenty kilograms?
Yes, you ran fast. Yes, I believe that again haha.
But our outfit was no joke, it was the outfit of someone running a full marathon.
Haha, both of them wearing sunglasses, haha
But he came in fifteen minutes later and uh, the feeling, the feeling.
I paid it, I got the feeling, ah, I have to drink.
Ah, I went to the first floor and Leo said, wait a minute.
Don't come down. First, install this camera.
I left it and went up again and came down the first time.
Pretending haha, there were three in the original vlog.
Yes, and I am in charge of content development.
That's me Hahaha
I found this reference
Yes, that's what I found. I'm going to use dry hair as a basic, and I can do it like this, or yes.
I wish I went with a slightly hip feel. Right now, I'm going to wear it like this.
It's the same and like this
I think I'll wear it and I'll tell you about K's hairstyle.
What kind of day will unfold today? It’s a fun day
Wow
Thank you. I feel relaxed today.
Eat it quickly
Um um I want to eat too
Oh, it's not that sweet, it's spinach
I ate it, but what flavor does it taste like? Oh, I want to eat chocolate. Chocolate.
Wow, there's chocolate underneath. It's amazing. Why does this have to be delicious too? Hey, it smells delicious.
Well, Jang Yu had both hands, why?
I got a follow
I can eat this when I eat a lot. Oh, I will eat it later. Later.
I Friend You Hair Stylist
I Friend You Hair Style
I plan your hairstyle
I plan I plan your hairstyle I plan your hairstyle
I plan your hairstyle I plan your hairstyle I plan your style
I keep thinking I should live in Korea
Wow, I was going to start by reading English, but hey, not yet.
I have some time. It's in English. Would you like to read it in English?
You'll know it because of the pronunciation. If you read it once, I'll tell you this.
We Warper Skype & Hair Test Beforeer Service I have to say this, yes.
do you want check this Skype just say it like this
Ah
No sudden meeting, I have a model haha
But I did this once in a hurry. Please stop once rather than just wandering around.
Oh, in between, but that's it
If you say you can't do it, then you're coming out to drag me out.
Ah, this is difficult. Now I made a note like this and opened it.
But it doesn't work, the reality is sad
do you like Manhattan Manhattan do you like Manhattan
Manhattan Manhattan
ah it's my sound is very bad menadin do you like menadin
what is that ah you like it
huh it happens oh do you like
it I'm very itchy some words I understand some are more difficult
I want more ah it's very hot you say it's very cute
Haha I just spoke Korean today
I can't go to the show. I'm having a hard time. Actually, my mouth is more important than my body right now.
It was hard. It wasn't going well, so I went to the academy from Monday to Saturday for three months.
I didn't even go to the beauty salon and just kept going to English classes. It's the best.
I wrote three notes, and the last one I wrote is truly an essential note.
He was a little girl, but when we came to the scene, he didn't show up.
Ha, really, what should I do? No, I should do better.
I thought so, but it seemed a bit professional and a bit reassuring.
I really wanted to say this too, but I'm so happy for you today too
I really wanted to do it
I can’t do even one thing. It’s okay. I’m already so happy for you today.
I'm so happy I'm also eating
Let’s give it a try today. Let’s give it a try today.
Now look, yes twenty-five
This is you. I will get ready. Yes, comfort, comfort, start, decorate, decorate, flower, decorate.
Have a hard time, have a hard time
uh welcome to the class captain yes hello yes
hello hi
Good morning Nice meet you Nice meet you Hello, this is Ana Ana Hello Ana
Oh, it's Ana, Ana, hi, Ana, Nice Meat You
I'm Anna I'm Anna
hi Anna nice to meet you I'm Anna yeah yeah oh should I take it
is it heavy oh
be careful uh alright
is it yeah
Yeah meet Rachel
hi Rachel
nice to meet you so let's go to the consultation room first great
you went to Korea for study
yes so it was in university
I went for a summer for two months
my name is Anna Maganto Ramirez I am a lawyer
I went in 2016 so nine years ago
for two months for a summer school program
where I helped teach young children English
and it interested me a lot in terms of Korean culture
how do you feel about like a makeover thing
I'm excited you're excited
I haven't done this before
oh really
yes
uh huh
Thank you for your hard work. Thank you for your hard work.
I like this week
hey hey don't make me jealous wait wait I'm the song
you know it OK
I really look at the money come on come on you like it's so funny
that's so
funny it's so funny it's so funny
one hand looks so much better than the other one
which one did you use
does anyone know how to do the egg yourself
no someone needs to teach me
someone sounds like a kind of egg yourself
oh wait you did the egg yourself pretty cool I did yeah
oh wrinkles
kindness sweetness is this for me
do you have any plan for today
and so my plan is to go out to dinner with my uh
namja chingu right my boyfriend but um
he doesn't know that we're having dinner yet OK
he's gonna feel so motion already OK
so I'm very excited alright uh huh
oh my God wow
have a seat here like this
yeah okay
oh hello
oh it's so cute
oh why are you surprised at this time
why I didn't see the back
the back yeah I love this volume
I can't believe that's all just my hair
uh huh oh okay let's go
oh okay
let's go um
I wanna be more romantic and soft
that's fine as long as I feel good in it
you know romantic and soft
great
yeah yeah so
the green's opposite colour is red right
so slightly put some red and burgundy
yeah burgundy ooh OK
it's like a glam look I want
so yeah let's do this
okay I'm gonna use this
and then I'm using copper brown
okay let's trade ahead
pancake pancake
pancack pancake
pancake pancake pancake yeah
the main is bling bling yeah
you love to blend out the eyeliner with the brown color eyeshadow
it makes it more natural or something
or yes and then deeper hmm
a lot
oh my God yes
yes that's crazy
sound good
look good
uh vintage
the paint uh huh
yeah you look so classy
I'm in the class with the ghost
you know it's a ghost you know it's a ghost
you know it's a ghost you
know it's a ghost you know it's a ghost
you know it's a ghost you know it's a ghost
do you use uh the eyebrow powder or any eyebrow product
I've never done anything to my eyebrows
no really
I've never done anything to my eyebrows no
oh really
would you mind if we trim a little
and make it a little different shape
is it okay um
I would prefer not uh huh
because I'm cause I'm Puerto Rican
I'm like Latino in my culture
having very strong eyebrows is like very big
uh huh so I think my eyebrows are very important to me
and then so yeah it's very good
actually uh
the balance the angle is different right
yeah so which is your
this is more this is your
so I'm gonna draw this side like like this
최대한 안 건드리면서 원래 느낌 벗어나지 않는 선에서 부드럽게 그리려고
노력을 했고요
yeah that's a lot better that's so crazy
that's so crazy huh
oh I love it me too yes definitely thank you
오 분 후면 오실 거 같아
I'm alright hi what's up I'm hey
hello great to meet you nice to meet you how are you
nice to meet you how are you nice to meet you hi great to meet you too
thank you so much it's a heavy one
hello hi yes how are you good how are you so have a seat here okay
okay
I like oh amazing
so we have Flower Mechanic with many videos that I wanted to pass yes
I do um
this banana bread well today wow
yeah so good yeah
I love your earrings oh my God
thank you that's so cute
thank you love gold
love bugs yeah
I love your style nice to meet you
I'm tell your hair stylist today
oh my God great
I'm so excited yeah
we are both also hair stylist yeah
we are both also hair stylist
아 이거 보시죠 헤어 스타일리스트 아우 세임잡 와
두 분 다 두 분 다 미용하시는구나
please follow me to the consultation room
how are you feeling about makeover today
yeah just do you like it yeah I'm excited I
love beauty and skin care
I can clearly see that you're just literally
so into fashion I'm so into it
any concern
I just turned 36 uh huh so I feel like my skin is changing
as I'm getting older yeah so my concern is maintaining
maintaining the healthiness of keep it good keep it fresh
oh my god this is so cute
oh my god
Haha oh wow it's really big
I heard that there is a good machine that can diagnose my current condition.
I'm thinking of giving it a try in New York.
You measure your skin type and
We recommend products that match the measurement results.
When you press the circle button, it clicks.
below
The color of the device you see in front of you will appear.
If you look at it like this, various items will appear. Below are the contents.
We will recommend ingredients that are right for you one by one. This is a recommendation. Yes.
Let me measure your nose. Yes, usually your forehead and nose should be measured a lot.
Collagen is a new product that can shrink both pores and horizontal pores.
The view is ZINK. ZINK. I think you can just leave like this.
Haha shall I finish it haha no
and then we're gonna zoom in and
see your face condition OK OK so your skin
oh you can see the pores here oh
right getting down to the nitty gritty yeah so this is amazing yeah
This technology is so cool yeah I know
you have like pores and sensitivity
to the top you know for sensitive skin and a little bit of for pores
clean out you know great she needs a overhaul yes I use a lot of
sunscreen that's a really good hack a lot of sunscreen
every 30 minutes yes I like being that's perfect 10
yeah sometimes you know people underestimate
how sunlight goes to you know toxic for your skin
I'm a cancer survivor so I don't need to add it yeah
I know yeah you're great
yeah I just like a look at your information and I'm so impressed
thank you
I'm Martha Ellen Maybury
and I own a hair salon here in New York in Brooklyn
it's actually my 18th anniversary of being in New York
um I was diagnosed with Hodgkin's lymphoma in the end of 2020
it's shocking you know like you can only prepare so much to lose
your looks and your hair
and you don't realize we think we're secure in ourselves
but these things are security blankets and
I do find that like I really cherish my hair now that I have it back
and so I want to take care of it and same with my skin and
I think we are done for today so amazing
let's move on to your makeup first woo ha ha ha okay
and I just wanted to give a you a big hug
oh my gosh yes of course
thank you for having me thank you
I'm so excited I'm really grateful to you know having you thank you
yeah yeah
thank you thank you so much okay
bring it hello
hi how are you
I'm Daniel I'm Daniel have a seat great
I'm so nervous cause you're a designer hahaha don't be nervous
I'm just I'm just beginner you know
oh yeah I I do my best alright
oh yeah I'm sure I'm sure it'll be perfect
have you ever tried this kind of mask before
um not this exact one but I do love a a little mask
let me show you this texture is so unique wow
like a speed right so cool this it feels so good today
it's like so warm out your makeup goes on flawlessly yay
how do I look
you look amazing
I'm gonna recline your chair okay so just relax wow
you can you can sleep though OK perfect alright
please sleep this time overdo for sleep alright do my best
how's the temperature it's good
is it good yes
so
yeah
so hold on why yes
when did you start doing hair
you know what
yeah I mean
just came here for this project
that's amazing yeah
I just Learned it amazing
but I Learned so hard that's great yeah
how was the trampoline it's perfect
you just so good
impressive
very impressive for not going to cosmetology school
haha
hello again hello again
perfect
okay oh hmm
your skin became clear and bright
yes
You're so pretty when you smile. When you smile, it's so refreshing and refreshing.
The cool and prepared look is now vintage.
Yellow and did you see his glasses? Wow.
Oh so fashionable
So now the two of you have to do your makeup like a peacock.
I have to go
only add one nice
not too not too much but the add I
I had to get very good at doing these because um
I I'm a cancer survivor I I'm a cancer survivor
so I lost all my hair and my lashes everything
yeah so I was putting wigs and wearing right fake lashes
oh my God yeah it was rough I almost cry oh no
so it's nice to have hair again
was it so hard right oh my gosh it's so hard you just never know
until you're in it and
would you mind if I asked
what is the hard which is hard part when you got a cancer hmm yeah so
I think the hardest part was
you just have to stop life
you know stop life
you stop life stops
everything stops you know
it's just like I was I own a business
so it's very hard to not be able to see my clients
cause my clients have been with me for years right
so it's hard to just
you cannot stop and focus on being healthy and treated
yeah
yeah and of course
losing the hair is not easy
yeah that was rough
This is the first year after the treatment
yes yeah
um it's been 4 years since I did my treatment
mm hmm because I feel more confident with it now right
um it's still
it's still getting thicker
I could use a lot of help in that arena
yeah oh
thank you yeah
totally
When I heard about it, I was really surprised.
Since you're so bright, I thought I'd only share some really interesting episodes.
But I found out that he was a person who had been fighting cancer for a long time.
I really can't even imagine how difficult it is, but
I'm so proud that you've overcome it and are sitting here, and it worked out so well.
I feel sad every moment
and let's add
sparkle and glitters on it
of 3 wow I love this yeah look at this oh that's a nice color yeah
the green highlighter wow today so cool
look at this in the shell shell so cute that's so cool
oh
wow
I love it
what do you think great
amazing looks so good so talented
he's so amazing yeah amazing thank you guys
yeah
what's up hi
how you doing good
how are you OK
hi your friend
this is Martha's other friend
this is Ryan hi
how are you hi
nice to meet you nice to meet you Ryan
Ryan Ryan
alright I'm Daniel
nice to meet you nice to meet you
I like this pants I know
I was trying to look cool
you do look cool yeah
we got like a K beauty stuff
we could try again really
and oh my God what's that
oh hahaha
just walk along just walk along hahaha
I look tired I need eye stuff hahaha
are you guys trying it yeah
how is it how is it
oh actually
I have their face wash
don't do that oh really
yeah you tried it
I'm just starting to run out of all the Korean products
I bought in Seoul
2 3 years ago
oh really
I bought so many many haha
so you still using it I probably had about 60 of the snail masks
I gave a lot of them away
oh serious
yeah I love that and it's a
yeah you're like Steph yeah you're like Steph
ah you the
you the her yeah
Anna's her boyfriend yeah
ah OK OK OK
OK Anna's boyfriend
yeah right
ah sorry
ah it's nice to meet you Daniel yeah
just have a seat please yeah
yeah Anna is coming
you're coming yeah
you should sit on the middle please
what's that Ryan can
you come Ryan can you come here please
sorry about that switch yeah hahaha
I think I'm assuming your girlfriend's Anna yeah
so she's gonna come first hahaha
like boyfriend
whatever whatever
close your eyes
she's done
interest me a lot in terms of Korean culture
I'm Mama Chika
oh wow do you remember
and so my plan is to go out to dinner with my uh Namda chingu right
my boyfriend
and everyone we love you
open your eyes thank you
Just keep the original color and
I thought it would be a good idea to do an updo while maintaining the volume.
I didn't realize my face could look so regal
but I kept my eyebrows so it still feels like me
open your eyes
beautiful
hahaha
don't touch the lipstick yeah yeah I don't want it
your hair looks amazing I know oh my God it's hair oh my God it's hair
oh
oh my God it's hair oh my God it's hair oh my God it's hair oh my God
it's hair oh my god it's hair oh
my God it's hair oh my God it's hair oh my God it's hair
oh my God it's hair oh my God it's hair
oh my God it's hair your so beautiful so ah
you're so cute now we have to go out to dinner oh yeah of course
It's really so cute. Boyfriend, he's so cute.
You're pretty now, you're cute, you're cute, oh so cute
It's cute thank you thank you thank you
I can't stop looking I know right
Thank you thank you bye bye
so cute oh hahaha it's it next next ooh
have you worked in the US oh no before first time that's exciting yeah
what do you think is it is it quite difference between Korean style
or US style um Americans are so fast oh yeah right with the Korean
style it's like there's just a little bit more attention to detail
I am right and care and like about the experience thoughtful
but we usually usually we do like
between 1 hour mm hmm we finish one out in 1 hour yeah yeah
사실 긴장이 많이 됐죠 헤어 디자이너들은 자기의 주관이 진짜
강하거든요 자기가 어떤 머리가 제 제일 잘
어울리는지 자기가 제일 잘 알고
그런 거죠 그래서 사실 고민을 많이 했어요
it's quite nervous cause you're yeah like good designer hahaha
she's nervous now no
have you seen Ryan uh I saw him from afar all right
Ryan is a very good friend of mine is he is he is he your step
uh your shop your salon yeah he's my client oh OK I uh I do his
I do his hair color and his haircut
yeah wow it's a very yeah beautiful
who is over there oh yeah right yeah I did all of his color
and his uh haircut
he's a good guy yeah
hahaha good looking guy I have very good friends I'm very lucky
I like volume volume is very important
oh that looks pretty OK volume OK
more volume I don't wanna lose too much volume OK
full volume is yeah
my hair is a lot finer now
don't worry about it you know yeah
you know I wanna keep volume OK
dry only dry today
oh leave it to me OK yes
여기 볼륨 살리는 게 좀 어려운 팁 중에 있거든요 그거를 제가
보여줬어요 한국에서 살리는 방법을 나이스 와 하하 땡큐 나이스
especially like in the blow drying like she did a different technique
where she heats
different parts of the hair and then like lets it rest
and then moves it's just more like
manipulating and sculpting the hair with the heat which was really
cool to see
이건 뭐
그래서 이거
today is very important day the big change in your hair yeah
I love adding extra hair oh really
yeah really I before I did chemotherapy um my hair was very long
and very thick my ponytail was like this thick
okay so very different now
that it grew back I'm glad to have hair but it's it's a lot
finer so it's nice to add more haha
makes me feel like my old self
it's I calling the your hair
OK OK yup yes wow it's very different to your chair ooh
ha ha ha ha OK
looks so natural it blended so well
oh my God you look so gorgeous who am I new person new person
so new person
oh my gosh it's so nice so nice thank you so much
K style done
it's in clothes you change the clothes
Smart Ellen paying for today
sitting here this whole time
what is Smart Ellen paying me today
you want me to bother her about it
oh hahaha
I'm doing this it's fun what part of it's fun
experience okay
should we go yeah
a lot of times coming yes
that time I was like okay
I figured it out you got it
I figured it out
it's terrible today
what if I don't like it you're gonna have to like it you look nice
ready
hahaha
I'm Martha Ellen Maybury
and I own a hair salon here in New York in Brooklyn
I was diagnosed with Hodgkin's lymphoma in in the end of 2020
and I did four months of chemotherapy
and went through the whole process of losing all my hair
and having to step away from work
I really cherish my hair now that I have it back
and so I want to take care of it and same with my skin
and I really like to have a makeover
dedicated to bringing out these things that I've been missing
a long time
okay she's coming
open it
open it oh my God
너무 밝고 그분 웃을 때 너무 예쁘세요 웃을
때 너무 그 청량하고 너무 시원 시원하고 정말 그냥 자유 그냥 팝한 거
what do you think I love it yeah
hello
it's so pretty it's so cool mm hmm because I could wear whatever
I want
I said rainbow challah, but the roots were a little frozen. Oh, it was so pretty.
mm hmm that's so cool
Because of that, I ended up with makeup that never left.
yeah my hair is a lot finer now don't worry about it haha you know
haha yeah
It's a bit of a difficult technique to bring out the volume here.
I showed you how to save lives in Korea.
so it's nice to add more makes me feel like my old self
something
yup it's Kenny C Yay
it's just really nice to see my hair long
again it's been a while since I like
saw it with like a nice shape
just made me feel like it's like the best version of seeing my skin
smooth and seeing like my eyes pop so just I feel flawless
when we push
you
oh my god
oh god can you hear it wow
okay oh my God yeah oh my God wow
hahaha
I have more hair oh my God you got more hair hahaha euphoria
haha
a lot of versions of you this is haha oh thank you wow
I have a shimmer too on you yeah alright my highlighter haha
so amazing yeah so talented feels wonderful yeah rainbow job
so nice oh my gosh so talented thank you I love it gorgeous so good
yeah thank you
ah so nice look at your your
it's writing your okay this is this is homepage
this is my website website how's her
she great yes yeah oh my it looks better than she usually does
hahaha bro
don't be no
she always looks like that hahaha
oh thank you so
so much this is so lovely
I'm so crazy thank you
it was such a lovely experience
your team is so amazing
this
hi hi hi
thank you so much thank you so
so much I'll send all the photos
have a good time thank you
keep health yeah
forever exactly
forever and ever
thank you
hahaha hahaha
bye
엄청 위험하다 이거 불만 사건이네 아
오늘 뮤직 페스티벌 기대된다 are you a very famous
hey Miriam I saw you on video that's a very beautiful face you have
aura that you have I also
broadcasted it to my manager oh
my God I just saw you on the video I thought
you were a superstar but you were a comedian oh
wow wow
touch touch
cause I'm addicted to your poison
ah ha no oh yeah you dancer yeah what the fuck exist hahaha
I'm sorry
Jordan Jordan Jordan Jordan and
ah ah ah ah out out out out out out out out I'm sorry
wow
so beautiful